{
    "subject": "resource/Courteney_Cox",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Courteney Bass Cox",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Courteney Cox is Courteney Bass Cox.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9810038208961487,
            "question": "Is 'Courteney Bass Cox' a real name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9773358106613159,
            "question": "What is Courteney Cox's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9374470710754395,
            "question": "What is the last name of Courteney Cox?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8980669379234314,
            "question": "What are the two middle names of Courteney Cox?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8943672776222229,
            "question": "What is the first name of Courteney Cox?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8939934372901917,
            "question": "What is the first part of Courteney Cox's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8729531168937683,
            "question": "How many parts make up Courteney Cox's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8071357607841492,
            "question": "Could you use Courteney's full name to address her formally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2322416603565216,
            "question": "If someone only knew her middle names, would they know her full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03441661596298218,
            "question": "Is it common for people to have three given names?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Courteney Cox is Courteney Bass Cox.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7357_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If someone only knew her middle names, would they know her full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7357_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you use Courteney's full name to address her formally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7357_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many parts make up Courteney Cox's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7357_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7357_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7357_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7357_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7357_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7357_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7357_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7357_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7357_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7357_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7357_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Courteney Cox's full name is Courteney Bass Cox, with variations such as Courteney Cox-Arquette noted in some files."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}